

Greater Orlando Area, FL 33837

mancylee7@gmail.com

646-761-2366

in linkedin.com/in/nancylee7

github.com/nancylee1

mancylee1.github.io

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

• C#

JAVA SCRIPT

SQL

HTML

CSS

ASP.NET
 DEBUGGING

WEB DESIGN

• ORM, DAPPER, API

#### **EDUCATION**

### **True Coders**

Full Stack Software Engineer

#### Baruch College - New York, NY Zicklin School of Business

BBA, Real Estate Finance & Investments, Business Law (4.0 GPA)

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Full Stack Software Engineering Certification - TrueCoders
- Construction Management NY Newman Real Estate Institute

# **RECOGNITIONS**

- Phi Eta Sigma
- Golden Key Award
- Baruch Writing Center Tutor
- Healthcare Knowledge in Dentistry

# NANCY LEE

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I am a passionate and responsible professional with excellent troubleshooting and communication skills. I am shifting from 13 years in financial services to focusing on my new career as a Software Engineer! I have experience in improving and updating software performance, as well as developing new software functionalities.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Homepoint Financial Corporation, Remote**

Senior Loan Processor

August 2020 - May 2022

- Introduced and spearheaded two software integrated solutions for securely e-signing necessary client due diligence documents in efforts to cut company costs
- Specially selected Project Implementation Operations team member for Quality Test Tech projects including Encompass' URLA, Mortgage Hippo, & CoreLogic Credco, etc. for company-wide rollouts
- Ranked #1 in Consumer Direct/Direct Origination Operations as Senior Processor for the past 12 months
  consecutively with \$7.1 Billion in closings
- Consistently awarded and recognized by colleagues and clients for excellent borrower contact and customer service in client facing position
- Immense Financial knowledge with ability to Review & Calculate income (fixed, salaried and selfemployed) and review Assets (large deposits), Business & Personal Taxes

# Marcus & Millichap Capital Corporation, New York, NY

March 2019 - April 2020

Commercial Loan Processor & Closer

- Extremely high-paced and competitive environment with extraordinary organizational skills to handle over 40 loan transactions on a day to day basis, closing average 85 loans/year totaling over \$200 million
- Excellent communication skills by working collaboratively with Loan Officers, Underwriters, clients, third
  party vendors, attorneys, Title & Escrow companies
- Punctual at meeting deadlines to ensure timely closings to lower overall transaction costs
- Thorough knowledge on reviewing Lender applications, Personal Financial Statements, tax returns, P&L's, assets & liabilities, rent rolls, third party reports (appraisals, environmental reports, surveys, insurance),
   Title, and physical site inspection reports; property engineering reports, zoning reports, and various lender required documents

#### Marcus & Millichap Real Estate Investment Services, New York, NY

Director of Transactions & Operations

November 2012 - March 2019

- Introduced new portfolio management method through spearheading the implementation and engineering of Salesforce CRM for portfolio management data analysis and tracking
- Spearheaded implementation of Pardot using Salesforce Marketing Cloud as a solution to marketing automation
- Developed and created new templates for investment client & executive management presentations including cash flow models, proposals of value, offering memorandums, pro forma projections, business expenses and restructuring leases
- Slashed administration costs 60% by negotiating pricing and fees while ensuring the continuation and enhancements of services
- Restructured the entire deal team for the company and solely handled interviews for hire with training of all teammates for each respective role
- Portfolio Management of Deals in Pipeline: \$240 million per day, averaging 490,000 Sq Ft, Closed and underwritten a total of \$33 billion worth of assets

# SEEKOR Property Management, New York, NY

November 2018 - November 2019

Portfolio Manager

 Built entire infrastructure for office space and software implementation for Startup Company from scratch within 12 months, working with construction and design teams

# SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Development: Visual Studio, VS Code, Git Hub/Bash, MySQL, Razor, Dapper, Figma

Vocational: MS Office Suite, Salesforce, AWS, Encompass, EllieMae AIQ, Mortgage Hippo, CoreLogic Credco, Credit Plus, Loansphere/Black Knight, Excel, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Publisher, Argus, Apto, Pardot, LexisNexis, CoStar, LandVision, Docutech, DocuSign

Graphic Design: Select Adobe Products: InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop